Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/thai-nguyen-quoc-7ab483259 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Agile Methodologies Business Development Project Management

Thai Nguyen Quoc

Project Manager

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Summary

An experienced civil engineer in the site structural works in residential projects with a completed educational background. Seeking a position where I can ultilize my managerial and engineering expertise to develop the company as well my long term career.

Experience

Stonex

4 years 1 month

Project Manager January 2024 - Present (1 year 3 months) Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

HIGHLIGHTED PROJECTS:

- Ecovillage Sai Gon River - Nhon Trach, Dong Nai Investor: Ecopark

- Akari City- Binh Tan District, HCMC

Investor: Nam Long Group

Site Manager

March 2021 - December 2023 (2 years 10 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

HIGHLIGHTED PROJECTS:

- The River Thu Thiem - District 2,HCMC

Investor: REFICO & CII

- T&T An Giang (Add: Long Xuyen District, An Giang Province) Investor: Vinh Thien Da Nang Ltd., Co a member of T&T Group

- The Global City - Thu Duc City, HCMC

Investor: Masterise Group

- Celadon City - District Tan Phu, HCMC

Investor: Gamuda Land

- Masteri Central Point - Thu Duc City, HCMC

Investor: Masterise Home

- The Nexus - District 1, HCMC

Investor: City Garden

ABOUT:

STONEX's vision is to become the most prestigious and most innovative stone supplier and contractor in Vietnam with sustainable values and international standard products by a creative, disciplined and dedicated team.

Website: https://stonex.vn/

CMT

Site Manager June 2020 - January 2021 (8 months)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

HIGHLIGHTED PROJECTS:

Wink Hotel Danang Centre - Danang Province

Investor: Wink Hotels

Ricons

Site Engineer September 2019 - April 2020 (8 months)

HIGHLIGHTED PROJECT:

- Zhaowen Knitting - Tay Ninh Province

Investor: Zhaowen Knitting Ltd., Co.

ABOUT:

Over 17 years of establishment and development since 2004, Ricons has delivered construction projects throughout the country, from high-rise buildings, hotels, resorts to factories and infrastructure.

Link to website: https://www.ricons.vn/?lang=en

Unicons Company Limited
Site Supervisor
December 2016 - August 2019 (2 years 9 months)

HIGHLIGHTED PROJECTS:

- Block P6 of Vinhome Central Park - Binh Thanh District, HCMC

Investor: Vinhomes

- Sala Campus of Vietnam Australia International School - District 2, HCMC

Investor: VAS

- A&B Central Square - Nha Trang Province

Investor: A&B Development Corp
- Masteri An Phu - District 2 HCMC

Investor: Maserise Home

ABOUT:

Investing in modern construction practices and management techniques to ensure that it remains at the cutting edge of our industry. Coteccons provide a comprehensive and optimal solution in the construction industry. Coteccons is the contractor of choice in Vietnam.

Wesite: https://coteccons.vn/en/

Education

Bach Khoa University (fomerly Ho Chi Minh City University of Technology)

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Building/Construction Site Management/ Manager · (September 2011 - April 2016)